{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Bathroom Fan Installers","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","__cache./api/resource/task/40241/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40241,"taskName":"Bath Exhaust Fan - Install","taskDescription":"Install a Bath Exhaust Fan","xmTaskDescriptor":"Bathroom Fan Installers","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":22,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Bath bathroom attic Replacement Fan","textMessagingName":"Inst Exhaust Fan","rolloverLongDesc":"This person can do the entire job of cutting a whole in the ceiling material, mounting the fan, making the electrical connection \u0026 routing the ductwork to the outdoors.","rolloverShortDesc":"Includes mounting, electrical connection \u0026 ducting.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Install a Bath Exhaust Fan.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Bathroom Fan Installation \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Bath Exhaust \u0026 Vent Fan Replacement","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":25,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Bath Exhaust Fan Install","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Bath Exhaust Fan - Install","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Bath Exhaust Fan Project","urlName":"Bath-Exhaust-Fan-Install","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Bathroom Fan Installation Pros - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor Exhaust \u0026 Vent Fan Replacement","searchKeywords":"Bath,bathroom,attic,Replacement,Fan,Exhaust, vent","emcCategoryOid":-12029,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":548,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40241/":{"taskOID":40241,"originalTaskOID":40241,"setID":548,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":3048,"questionDisplayText":"What are needs?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What best describes your needs?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4090,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Need to replace an existing bath fan","answerDisplayText":"Need to replace an existing bath fan","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4084,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Need to install a bath fan in a new location","answerDisplayText":"Need to install a bath fan in a new location","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4085,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Need to install a bath fan in a new location and run ductwork","answerDisplayText":"Need to install a bath fan in a new location and run ductwork","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":3049,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Fan","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of bath exhaust fan do you want?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6043,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Standard exhaust fan","answerDisplayText":"Standard exhaust fan","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1496,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Combination fan and heater","answerDisplayText":"Combination fan and heater","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1497,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Combination fan and light","answerDisplayText":"Combination fan and light","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1498,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Combination fan, heater and light","answerDisplayText":"Combination fan, heater and light","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8031,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Want recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Want recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":3048,"questionDisplayText":"What are needs?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What best describes your needs?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4090,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Need to replace an existing bath fan","answerDisplayText":"Need to replace an existing bath fan","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4084,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Need to install a bath fan in a new location","answerDisplayText":"Need to install a bath fan in a new location","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4085,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Need to install a bath fan in a new location and run ductwork","answerDisplayText":"Need to install a bath fan in a new location and run ductwork","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":4090,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Need to replace an existing bath fan","answerDisplayText":"Need to replace an existing bath fan","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4084,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Need to install a bath fan in a new location","answerDisplayText":"Need to install a bath fan in a new location","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4085,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Need to install a bath fan in a new location and run ductwork","answerDisplayText":"Need to install a bath fan in a new location and run ductwork","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":3049,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Fan","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of bath exhaust fan do you want?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6043,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Standard exhaust fan","answerDisplayText":"Standard exhaust fan","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1496,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Combination fan and heater","answerDisplayText":"Combination fan and heater","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1497,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Combination fan and light","answerDisplayText":"Combination fan and light","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1498,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Combination fan, heater and light","answerDisplayText":"Combination fan, heater and light","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8031,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Want recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Want recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":6043,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Standard exhaust fan","answerDisplayText":"Standard exhaust fan","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1496,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Combination fan and heater","answerDisplayText":"Combination fan and heater","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1497,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Combination fan and light","answerDisplayText":"Combination fan and light","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1498,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Combination fan, heater and light","answerDisplayText":"Combination fan, heater and light","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8031,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Want recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Want recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]}}